let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the highest grossing anime film of all time?",
    answer: "Mugen Train",
    options: [
      "Grave Of The Fireflies",
      "Your Name",
      "Mugen Train",
      "Dragon Ball Super: Broly"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the first anime ever produced?",
    answer: "Nakamura Gatana",
    options: [
      "Nakamura Gatana",
      "Sailor Moon",
      "Neon Genesis Evangelion",
      "Rurouni Kenshin"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What popular anime features a notebook that can kill people by writing their names in it?",
    answer: "Death Note",
    options: [
      "Love Tyrant",
      "Death Parade",
      "Death Note",
      "FullMetal Alchemist"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What anime has a protagonist who aims to become the Pirate King?",
    answer: "One Piece",
    options: [
      "One Piece",
      "Sol Bianca: The Legacy",
      "Queen Emeraldas",
      "Bodacious Space Pirates"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In Naruto, what is the highest rank a ninja can achieve?",
    answer: "Hokage",
    options: [
      "Chūnin",
      "Hokage",
      "Jōnin",
      "Genin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the giant humanoid creatures in ‘Attack on Titan’?",
    answer: "Titans",
    options: [
      "Titans",
      "Monsters",
      "Demons",
      "Colossus"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the name of the virtual world in ‘Sword Art Online’?",
    answer: "Aincrad",
    options: [
      "Underworld",
      "Gun Gale",
      "Alfheim",
      "Aincrad"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is the highest-ranking hero in ‘One Punch Man’?",
    answer: "Blast",
    options: [
      "Blast",
      "Tornado of Terror",
      "Drive Knight",
      "Silver Fang"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the unique power system in ‘Hunter x Hunter’ called?",
    answer: "Nen",
    options: [
      "Cursed Energy",
      "Ki",
      "Nen",
      "Chakra"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the name of the currency in ‘One Piece’?",
    answer: "Belly",
    options: [
      "Belly",
      "Zeni",
      "Double Dollar",
      "Woolong"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What’s the name of Goku’s wife in the ‘Dragon Ball’ series?",
    answer: "Chi-Chi",
    options: [
      "Mai",
      "Bulma",
      "Chi-Chi",
      "Caulifla"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What type of food does Naruto Uzumaki love the most?",
    answer: "Ramen",
    options: [
      "Dango",
      "Ramen",
      "Curry Of Life",
      "Onigiri"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who is the ‘Fullmetal Alchemist’?",
    answer: "Edward Elric",
    options: [
      "Alphonse Elric",
      "Ling Yao",
      "Roy Mustang",
      "Edward Elric"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "In ‘Neon Genesis Evangelion’, what are the giant bio-machines piloted by the main characters called?",
    answer: "Evangelions",
    options: [
      "Evangelions",
      "Angels",
      "Gurren Lagann",
      "Getter Robo"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What is the main sport featured in ‘Haikyuu!!’?",
    answer: "Volleyball",
    options: [
      "Tennis",
      "Soccer",
      "Basketball",
      "Volleyball"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Who is the founder and first Hokage of the Hidden Leaf Village in ‘Naruto’?",
    answer: "Hashirama Senju",
    options: [
      "Tobirama Senju",
      "Hashirama Senju",
      "Hiruzen Sarutobi",
      "Tsunade"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "In ‘My Hero Academia’, what is All Might’s quirk?",
    answer: "One For All",
    options: [
      "All For One",
      "Whirlwind",
      "One For All",
      "Shield"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Who is the original creator of the ‘One Piece’ manga?",
    answer: "Eiichiro Oda",
    options: [
      "Eiichiro Oda",
      "Tatsuki Fujimoto",
      "Akira Toriyama",
      "Makoto Yukimura"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "In ‘JoJo’s Bizarre Adventure’, what are the supernatural abilities used by characters known as?",
    answer: "Stands",
    options: [
      "Geass",
      "Rinnegan",
      "Ultra Instinct",
      "Stands"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Who is the protagonist of ‘Fairy Tail’?",
    answer: "Natsu Dragneel",
    options: [
      "Erza Scarlet",
      "Natsu Dragneel",
      "Lucy Heartfilia",
      "Grey Fullbuster"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "In ‘Tokyo Ghoul’, what do ghouls eat?",
    answer: "Human flesh",
    options: [
      "Nothing",
      "Burger King",
      "Coffee",
      "Human flesh"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "In ‘Death Note’, what is the name of the Shinigami who drops the Death Note?",
    answer: "Ryuk",
    options: [
      "Ryuk",
      "Midora",
      "Rem",
      "Sidoh"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "Who is the protagonist in ‘Inuyasha’?",
    answer: "Inuyasha",
    options: [
      "Kagome",
      "Shippo",
      "Inuyasha",
      "Kirara"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "In ‘Hunter x Hunter’, what is the name of Gon’s father?",
    answer: "Ging Freecss",
    options: [
      "Isaac Netero",
      "Ging Freecss",
      "Pariston Hill",
      "Gashta Bellam"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "In ‘One Punch Man’, who is Saitama’s disciple?",
    answer: "Genos",
    options: [
      "Metal Bat",
      "Zombieman",
      "King",
      "Genos"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Who solved the Millennium Puzzle?",
    answer: "Yugi Mutou",
    options: [
      "Seto Kaiba",
      "Maximillion Pegasus",
      "Yugi Mutou",
      "Yami Bakura"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Which anime series revolves around a boy who sells his soul to a demon?",
    answer: "Black Butler",
    options: [
      "Naruto",
      "Black Butler",
      "Blue Exorcist",
      "Claymore"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Whose body gained the properties of rubber after unintentionally eating a Devil Fruit?",
    answer: "Monkey D. Luffy",
    options: [
      "Monkey D. Luffy",
      "Prince Grus",
      "Charlotte Katakuri",
      "Marco"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "In the anime ‘Claymore’, who was the most powerful of the ‘Awakened Beings’?",
    answer: "Priscilla",
    options: [
      "Irene",
      "Rosemary",
      "Teresa",
      "Priscilla"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "In ‘Clannad’, when Sanae first met Okazaki, which kind of bread does she offer to him?",
    answer: "Sweet Bean Bread",
    options: [
      "Sweet Bean Bread",
      "Red Bean Bun",
      "Dango",
      "Ramen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Which is the first song used as an opening for ‘Naruto’?",
    answer: "‘Rocks’ by Hound Dog",
    options: [
      "‘Lovers’ by Seven Oops",
      "‘Empty Hearts’ by Anly",
      "‘Rocks’ by Hound Dog",
      "‘Far Away’ by Asian Kung-Fu Generation"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question: "Who was the first member of the First Levi Squad to die in ‘Attack on Titan’?",
    answer: "Gunther",
    options: [
      "Eld",
      "Gunther",
      "Petra",
      "Connie"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question: "As prophesied, Goku transformed into the Super Saiyan form in ‘Dragon Ball Z’. Where did this transformation take place?",
    answer: "Planet Namek",
    options: [
      "Eros",
      "Planet Arlia",
      "Planet Vegeta",
      "Planet Namek"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question: "This pink-haired girl is completely obsessed with her love for Yuki, which she professes in her ‘Yukiteru diary’. Who is she?",
    answer: "Yuno Gasai",
    options: [
      "Minene Uryuu",
      "Tsubaki Kasugano",
      "Yuno Gasai",
      "Ai Mikami"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "Which anime series involves a family possessed by the animals of the Chinese zodiac?",
    answer: "Fruits Basket",
    options: [
      "Fairy Tail",
      "Sailor Moon",
      "Jūni Taisen",
      "Fruits Basket"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 36,
    question: "What was the first feature-length anime?",
    answer: "Momotaro: Sacred Sailors",
    options: [
      "Momotaro: Sacred Sailors",
      "Horus: Prince of the Sun",
      "Castle in the Sky",
      "My Neighbor Totoro"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Who is known as the ‘One Punch Man’?",
    answer: "Saitama",
    options: [
      "King",
      "Saitama",
      "Bushidrill",
      "Twin Tail"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "What is the name of Speed Racer’s girlfriend?",
    answer: "Trixie",
    options: [
      "Kurio", 
      "Sparky",
      "Junko",
      "Trixie"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Who was the first character in ‘Dragon Ball Z’ who achieved the Super Saiyan 2?",
    answer: "Gohan",
    options: [
      "Goku", 
      "Gohan",
      "Vegeta",
      "Trunks"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "Which anime series centers around a warrior named Kenshiro?",
    answer: "Fist of the North Star",
    options: [
      "Fist of the North Star", 
      "Baki",
      "Trigun",
      "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"
    ]
  },
    
];

